businessesforsale.com 2016-11-29

# Dynamis' Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: 30 May 2014**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We have established this statement as a testament to our commitment to your privacy.

This Privacy Policy relates to the use of any personal information you provide to us through Dynamis websites and its partner websites (“our websites”) (where this policy appears in relation to the collection of information). Dynamis websites include, but are not limited to, BusinessesForSale.com (“the site”) FranchiseSales.com, PropertySales.com and FranchiseAVendre.fr.

**“Dynamis” includes Dynamis Ltd and Dynamis APAC Pty Ltd.** For more information about these companies please see our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.businessesforsale.com/cobrands/global/info/termsConditions.aspx).

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions during registration or the sending of an enquiry, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Our Privacy Policy was last updated in May 2014 and is effective upon acceptance for new users. By continuing to use Dynamis websites or otherwise continuing to deal with us, you accept this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of personal information

Anyone can browse our websites without revealing any personally identifiable information.

However, should you wish to contact a business for sale, a franchise opportunity or an intermediary, we will require you to provide some personal information.

Should you wish to advertise your services, your business (es) or your franchise opportunity, we will require you to provide some personal information.

By providing personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the UK.

We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * your name, email address, physical address, telephone numbers, and (depending on the service used), your business information, financial information, such as credit / payment card details or bank account numbers;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the site;
  * information that you disclose in a forum on any of our websites, feedback, correspondence through our websites, and correspondence sent to us;
  * other information from your interaction with our websites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information;
  * supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to Dynamis or one of our websites, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law; or if the information you provide cannot be verified, we may ask you to send us additional information, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your information).

## How we use your information

The primary reason we collect your personal information is to improve the services we deliver to you through our websites. By registering or sending an enquiry through one of our websites, you agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * connect you with relevant parties: 
    * If you are a buyer we will pass some or all of your details on to the seller / intermediary along with any message you have typed. This allows the seller to contact you in order to pursue a possible sale of a business;
    * If you are a seller / intermediary, we will disclose your details where you have given us permission to do so;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions;
  * customise, measure and improve our services, conduct internal market research, provide content and advertising;
  * tell you about other Dynamis websites, products and services, target marketing, send you service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences.

## Our disclosure of your information

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content infringes the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.

## We may also share your personal information with

When you select to register an account as a business buyer, you provide your personal details and we will pass this on to a seller of a business or franchise when you request more information.

When you select to register an account as a business broker or seller on the site, we provide a public platform on which to establish your business profile. This profile consists of pertinent facts about your business along with your personal information; namely, the contact information you provide to facilitate contact between you and other users' of the site. Direct email addresses and telephone numbers will not be publicly displayed on BusinessesForSale.com unless you specifically include it on your profile.

The information a user includes within the forums provided on the site is publicly available to other users' of the site. Please be aware that any personal information you elect to provide in a public forum may be used to send you unsolicited messages; we are not responsible for the personal information a user elects to disclose within their public profile, or in the private communications that users' engage in on the site.

We post testimonials on the site obtained from users'. These testimonials may include the name, city, state or region and business of the user. We obtain permission from our users' prior to posting their testimonials on the site. We are not responsible for any personal information a user selects to include within their testimonial.

When you elect to email a friend about the site, or a particular business, we request the third party's email address to send this one time email. We do not share this information with any third parties for their promotional purposes and only store the information to gauge the effectiveness of our referral program.

We may share your personal information with our service providers where necessary. We employ the services of a payment processor to fulfil payment for services purchased on the site.

BusinessesForSale.com works with a number of partners or affiliates, where we provide marketing services for these companies. These third party agents collect your personal information to facilitate your service request and the information submitted here is governed by their privacy policy.

## Masking Policy

In some cases, where the third party agent collects your information, the affiliate portal may appear within a BusinessesForSale.com frame. It is presented as a BusinessesForSale.com page for a streamlined user interface however the data collected on such pages is governed by the third party agent's privacy policy.

## Legal Disclosure

In certain circumstances, we may be legally required to disclose information collected on the site to law enforcement, government agencies or other third parties. We reserve the right to disclose information to our service providers and to law enforcement or government agencies where a formal request such as in response to a court order, subpoena or judicial proceeding is made. Where we believe in good faith that disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical or financial harm, or loss, or in protecting against illegal activity on the site, we reserve to disclose information.

Should the company undergo the merger, acquisition or sale of some or all of its assets, your personal information may likely be a part of the transferred assets. In such an event, your personal information on the site, would be governed by this privacy statement; any changes to the privacy practices governing your information as a result of transfer would be relayed to you by means of a prominent notice on the Site, or by email.

## Using information from Dynamis websites

In certain cases, (where you are receiving contact details of buyers interested in your business opportunity or a business opportunity you represent), you must comply with data protection laws, and give other users a chance to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them.

You agree to use Dynamis user information only for:

  * Dynamis transaction-related purposes that are not unsolicited commercial messages;
  * using services offered through Dynamis websites, or
  * other purposes that a user expressly chooses.

## Marketing

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Where you explicitly express your consent at the point of collection to receive offers from third party partners or affiliates, we will communicate to you on their behalf. We will not pass your information on.

You will receive email marketing communications from us throughout the duration of your relationship with our websites. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us you may unsubscribe and / or change your preferences at any time by following instructions included within a communication or emailing Customer Services.

If you have an account with one of our websites you can also log in and click the email preferences link to unsubscribe and / or change your preferences.

Please note that we reserve the right to send all website users notifications and administrative emails where necessary which are considered a part of the service. Given that these messages aren't promotional in nature, you will be unable to opt-out of them.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file written to your hard drive that contains information about you. Cookies do not contain any personal information about users. Once you close your browser or log out of the website, the cookie simply terminates. We use cookies so that we can personalise your experience of our websites.

If you set up your browser to reject the cookie, you may still use the website however; doing so may interfere with your use of some aspects of our websites. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). We have no access to or control over these cookies.

For more information about how BusinessesForSale.com uses cookies please read our [Cookie Policy.](http://www.businessesforsale.com/info/cookiePolicy.aspx)

## Spam, spyware or spoofing

We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your email preferences so we can communicate with you, as you prefer. Please add us to your safe senders list. To report spam or spoof emails, please contact us using the contact information provided in the Contact Us section of this privacy statement.

You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would breach our Terms and Conditions. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content. We may also store these messages for back up purposes only.

If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community (via Email-to-a-friend or other tools), we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses.

## Account protection

Your password is the key to your account. Make sure this is stored safely. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify us and change your password.

## Accessing, reviewing and changing your personal information

You can view and amend your personal information at any time by logging in to your account online. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate.

If at any time you wish to close your account, please [contact Customer Services](http://www.businessesforsale.com/feedback.aspx) and instruct us to do so. We will process your request as soon as we can.

You may also contact us at any time to find out what information we hold about you, what we do with it and ask us to update it for you.

We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

## Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the UK. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use a variety of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no method of security is 100% effective and while we take every measure to protect your personal information, we make no guarantees of its absolute security.

We employ the use of SSL encryption during the transmission of sensitive data across our websites.

## Third parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on our websites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Dynamis does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable.

We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## General

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time as we add new products and applications, as we improve our current offerings, and as technologies and laws change. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page.

Any changes will become effective upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on our affected websites. We will provide notice to you if these changes are material and, where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent. This notice may be provided by email, by posting notice of the changes on our affected websites or by other means, consistent with applicable laws.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, and you can’t find the answer to your question on our help pages, please contact us [using this form](http://www.businessesforsale.com/feedback.aspx) or email bfshelpatBusinessesForSale.com, telephone us at +44 (0) 20 7324 1930 or write to us at Dynamis House, 6-8 Sycamore Street, London, EC1Y 0SW, United Kingdom.

All customers based in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region are looked after by our Australian office. You can also [use this form](http://www.businessesforsale.com/feedback.aspx) or email us at bfshelpatBusinessesForSale.com. Alternatively you can write to us at BusinessesForSale.com, Level 33, Australia Square, 264 George Street, Sydney NSW 2000, Australia.
